Finding aid for Mike Wallace CBS/60 Minutes Papers, 1922-2007
Bentley Historical Library
- 60 Minutes Program Files
  - Season XXI, October 1988-September 1989
    - "Cpl. Bracy's Confession" (interview with former Marine Corporal Arnold Bracy, accused of allowing Soviet spies into sensitive areas of the US Embassy in Moscow), February 12, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - "Yasser Arafat" (interview), February 19, 1989
      - Background, 3 folders (Box 41)
      - Transcript (Box 41)
    - "Strom vs. Boeing" (Robert Strom, suing Boeing Company, claiming their EMP (electromagnetic energy produced from a nuclear explosion) testing led to his and his co-workers' leukemia), March 5, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Transcript (not labeled 'final transcript') (Box 42)
    - "1000 Per Cent Inflation" (how Brazilians are coping with very high inflation), March 12, 1989
      - Background, 3 folders (Box 42)
      - Transcript (Box 42)
    - "Estonia,", March 26, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - "Insane by Choice" (Gena Spero, defendant in a Massachusetts murder case that has not come to trial because she will not take the antipsychotic medication that would make her capable of testifying), April 2, 1989
      - Background (Box 42)
      - Transcript (Box 42)
    - "RU 486" (controversial new abortion pill available only in France), April 9, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Transcript (Box 42)
    - "Alfred Hempel" (report on former German Army officer and alleged principal black market supplier of nuclear products to third-world countries trying to manufacture A-Bombs), April 16, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Summer repeats and updates (memorandum from producer) (Box 42)
    - "Sad Day for the F.B.I." repeat (original air date: September 14, 1986), Transcript, April 30, 1989 (Box 42)
    - "Sue the Doctors" (increased medical malpractice suits and rising insurance premiums are forcing obstetricians out), May 7, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 42)
      - Transcript (Box 42)
    - "The Alliance" (The Alliance, a group of California lawyers and law firms controlled by Los Angeles attorney Lynn Stites, charged with defrauding insurance companies), Background, May 21, 1989 (Box 42)
    - "The Ayatollah" repeat (original air date: November 18, 1979), Update Material, June 4, 1989 (Box 42)
    - "To Get Rich is Glorious" repeat (original air date: September 7, 1986), Update Materials, June 11, 1989 (Box 42)
    - Repeats, Summer 1989 (Box 43)
    - "The Pollards" repeat (original air date: November 20, 1988), Update Materials, June 18, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "The Mercenary and the Mouthpiece" repeat (original air date: February 9, 1986), Update Materials, June 25, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "Robert Maxwell" repeat (original air date: December 4, 1988), Update Materials, July 23, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "Estonia" repeat (original air date: March 26, 1989), Update Materials, August 6, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "Merv's Money" repeat (original air date: February 5, 1989), Update Materials, August 13, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "RU 486" repeat (original air date: April 9, 1989), Update Materials, August 20, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "1000 Per Cent Inflation" repeat (original air date: March 12, 1989), Update Materials, September 3, 1989 (Box 43)
    - "Insane by Choice?" repeat (original air date: April 2, 1989), Update Materials, September 10, 1989 (Box 43)
  - Season XXII, September 1989-September 1990
    - "Voyage of Discovery" (the unprecedented inspection tour of highly sensitive Soviet military installations by Admiral William Crowe, Chairman, Joint Chiefs of Staff), September 17, 1989
      - Background, 3 folders (Box 43)
      - Transcript (Box 43)
    - "Taylor's Kids" (wealthy Louisiana oilman Patrick Taylor, who has promised to pay college tuition for several New Orleans inner city students if they meet certain standards in high school), September 24, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Transcript (Box 43)
    - "Harm's Way" (Genisco Technology Corporation, whose employees falsified test results on a HARM missile component), October 8, 1989
      - Background (Box 43)
      - Transcript (Box 43)
    - "My Turn" (interview with former First Lady Nancy Reagan about her forthcoming book My Turn), October 15, 1989
      - Briefing Book (Box 43)
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Transcript (Box 43)
    - "Felix Rodriguez" (interview with former CIA member, involved in many agency operations in Latin America and Vietnam since 1960), October 22, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 43)
      - Transcript (Box 43)
    - "U.S.S. Iowa" (alleged serious flaws in the US Navy's investigation of the explosion on the battleship), November 5, 1989
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Transcript (Box 44)
    - "Till Death Us Do Part" (increase of suicides among the elderly), Background, November 19, 1989 (Box 44)
    - "40,000 A Day" (high mortality rate among children in third world countries, (focusing on Tanzania), mostly due to malnutrition and preventable disease), November 26, 1989
      - Background, 5 folders (Box 44)
      - Transcript (Box 44)
    - "A View From the Other Side" (interview with Soviet spokesman Genadii Gerasimov), December 3, 1989
      - Background (Box 44)
      - Transcript (Box 44)
    - "The Last Gulag" (French videotaped report on life inside Perm 35, the last camp holding political prisoners in the USSR, presented by Wallace and commented on by Anatoly Sharansky), December 10, 1989
      - Background (Box 44)
      - Transcript (Box 44)
    - "The Minister of Cocaine" update (original air date: March 1, 1981), Update Materials, December 17, 1989 (Box 44)
    - "Vladimir Horowitz" repeat (original air date: December 26, 1977), Update Materials, December 24, 1989 (Box 44)
    - "Helen Hayes" repeat (original air date: December 4, 1983), Update Materials, December 31, 1977 (Box 44)
    - "Justice in a Company Town" (two drug-related arrests in Fort Mill, South Carolina, a textile town dominated by Spring Industries; the factory worker was sentenced to two years; the son of the owner did not get a jail sentence), Background, January 7, 1990 (Box 44)
    - "Melinda" (interview with 12-year-old muscular dystrophy victim Melinda Lawrence, who has written a book called My Life), January 14, 1990
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Transcript (Box 44)
    - "Want to be your own boss", January 16, 1990 (Box 44)
      (bluesheet only)
    - "Life or Death" (the last days of convicted murderer Dalton Prejean, on Louisiana's death row), January 21, 1990
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 44)
      - Briefing Book (Box 44)
    - "The McMartin Pre-School" update (original air date: November 2, 1986), February 4, 1990
      - Update Materials, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - "Joseph Stalin" (Memorial, an unofficial Soviet group publicizing Stalin's atrocities), February 11, 1990
      - Background, 6 folders (Box 45)
    - "Stealth" (the Stealth Bomber), February 18, 1990
      - Background (Box 45)
      - Transcript (Box 45)
    - "The Gospel According to Saxon" (controversial high school textbook author John Saxon), March 4, 1990
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 45)
      - Post-Show (Box 45)
    - "Who Shot Ernestine Perea?" (Wyoming criminal investigation resulting in the imprisonment of an innocent man, and the national shortage of forensic pathologists), March 18, 1990
      - Background, 2 folders (Box 45)
    - The Walkers, March 25, 1990 (Box 106)
    - Daily News and Unions, April 1, 1990 (Box 106)
    - "Slava" (Mstislav Rostropovich), April 8, 1990 (Box 106)
    - "Meth" (Methamphetamine), April 22, 1990 (Box 106)
    - The Alliance (repeat), April 29, 1990 (Box 106)
    - "Donna and Ricardo's baby" (update of 1988 feature), April 29, 1990, 1988-1990 (Box 106)
    - Torture of a PFC, James Griffin, May 6, 1990 (Box 106)
    - Who shall live?, May 13, 1990 (Box 107)
    - Thirty-six hour day (repeat), June 3, 1990 (Box 107)
    - Summer repeats (Box 107)
    - Special Mike Wallace: Then and Now, September 26, 1990 (Box 107)
    - Education special (Box 107)
  - Season XXIII, September 1990-September 1991
    - Who killed Gerald Bull?, September 16, 1990 (Box 107)
    - "Victims of Just Cause" (Panama casualties), September 30, 1990 (Box 107)
    - "Iran: 10 years later", October 21, 1990 (Box 108)
    - Salmon Rushdie, October 28, 1990 (Box 108)
    - "Bad cops" (Oakland housing police), November 4, 1990 (Box 108)
      (no file received for this program)
    - "If push comes to shove" (ADATS), November 11, 1990 (Box 108)
    - "Friday night lights" (Buzz Bessinger), November 25, 1990 (Box 108)
    - Temple Mount murder, December 2, 1990 (Box 108)
    - Michael McGee of Milwaukee, December 9, 1990; 2 folders (Box 109)
    - T.V. Millions, December 23,1990, 2 folders (Box W3)
    - Combat stress, January 6,1991 (Box 109)
    - "Iraqi Terror", January 13, 1991 (Box 109)
    - "Inferno" (Kuwaiti oil fields), January 20, 1991 (Box 109)
    - Moscow, February 3, 1991 (Box 109)
    - "A Letter from Jermarr" (Jermarr Arnold), February 17, 1991 (Box 109)
    - "My family is missing" (The Feltus Family), March 3, 1991 (Box 109)
    - "The Washington Monument" (Clark Clifford), March 17, 1991 (Box 110)
      (include 1990 interview with CC)
    - "The Trials of Mike Dowd", March 24, 1991 (Box 110)
    - "Brucification!" (Bruce Cutler), April 7, 1991 (Box 110)
    - "Nixon and Russia", April 14, 1991 (Box 110)
    - "War Games" (Japan Technology), April 21, 1991 (Box 110)
    - "Senator Alphonse D'Amato", April 28, 1991 (Box 110)
    - Mustard gas, June 16, 1991 (Box 110)
    - June 23, 1991 (Box 111)
      (Soviet retrospective)
    - Repeats, 1991 (Box 111)
    - September 25, 1991 (Box 111)
      (Soviet Coup)
  - Season XXIV, September 1991-June 1992
    - September 15, 1991 (Box 111)
      (Live or Die)
    - September 29, 1991 (Box 111)
      ("1-800-Con Man"; credit card fraud)
    - October 6, 1991 (Box 111)
      (Choice in schools)
    - October 20, 1991 (Box 111)
      (Iowa revisited)
    - November 3, 1991 (Box 111)
      ("George Bush vs. George Bush" combined with Population/Mexico)
    - November 17, 1991 (Box 111)
      ("Iraqi nuclear program")
    - November 24, 1991 (Box 111)
      ("Barbra")
    - December 8, 1991 (Box 112)
      (Mississippi Christmas Tree)
    - December 15, 1991 (Box 112)
      ("Take the Money and Run"; Deadbeat Doctors)
    - December 29, 1991 (Box 112)
      (Rikers Island)
    - January 12, 1992 (Box 112)
      ("Black Market Babies"-Tennessee Children's Home Society scandal)
    - January 19, 1992 (Box 112)
      (Father Greg Boyle)
    - February 2, 1992 (Box 112)
      ("The Russians are Coming" to Israel)
    - February 16, 1992 (Box 112)
      (Villain or victim?)
    - March 1, 1992 (Box 112)
      (Rogue Warrior; also called Red Cell)
    - March 29, 1992 (Box W3)
      (Henry Kissinger)
    - May 10, 1992 (Box 113)
      (Genes)
    - May 17, 1992 (Box 113)
      (California doctor murder conviction)
    - Updates, 1992 (Box 113)
    - June 17, 1992 (Box 113)
      ("Watergate: The Secret Story" CBS documentary)
  - Season XXV, September 1992-June 1993
    - September 13, 1992 (Box 113)
      (Gay cops)
    - September 20, 1992 (Box 114)
      (Christopher Dragoul)
    - October 4, 1992 (Box 114)
      ("Made in the U.S.A.")
    - November 1, 1992 (Box 114)
      (The Chairman Henry Gonzalez)
    - November 1992 (Box 114)
      (Election night coverage)
    - November 8, 1992 (Box 114)
      (Kirk Douglas)
    - November 29, 1992 (Box 114)
      (Parricide)
    - December 6, 1992 (Box 114)
      (Marilyn Horne)
    - December 20. (Pan AM 103), 1992 (Box 115)
    - January 3, 1993 (Box 115)
      (Alexander Zuyev)
    - January 10, 1993 (Box 115)
      ("Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms, and Harassment")
    - January 17, 1993 (Box 115)
      ("A hand in the till"; South Carolina political corruption)
    - January 24, 1993 (Box 115)
      ("Michael Carey, M.D.")
      (includes materials from viewers relating to cat shooting for medical purposes)
    - February 7, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("War criminal?: Bosnia atrocities)
    - February 21, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("Totaled"; automobile rip-offs)
    - February 28, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("Sharks don't get cancer"; use of shark cartilage in cancer treatment)
    - March 7, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("The Rev. Sharpton")
      (includes photographs)
    - March 21, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("The Archbishop"; sexual abuse in Catholic Church New Mexico)
    - March 28, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("Hongcouver")
    - April 11, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("Joint venture"; fetuses for sale)
    - April 18, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("Sidney Rittenberg")
    - May 16, 1993 (Box 116)
      ("Rock Newman" manager of Riddick Bowe)
      (includes photos)
    - Repeats, 1993 (Box 117)
  - Season XXVI, September 1993-March 1994
    - September 12, 1993 (Box 117)
      (California prisons, Pelican Bay)
    - September 19, 1993 (Box 117)
      (U.N. Waste)
    - September 26, 1993 (Box 117)
      (Pavarotti)
    - October 10, 1993 (Box 117)
      (Propaganda in the classroom)
    - (Equal justice or The Getaway drivers) (re Katherine Ann Power/Joe Yandle parole hearings), February 6, 1994 (Box W2)
    - March 13, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Murderer in Law School, James Hamm)
    - March 20, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Holocaust deniers)
  - Season XXVII, September 1994-September 1995
    - September 11, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Robert "Bud" MacFarlane)
    - October 2, 1994 (Box 118)
      ("An Exercise In Hypocrisy?" Bosnia war crimes)
    - October 16, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Limone allele)
    - October 30, 1994 (Box 118)
      (NOPD Blues)
    - November 6, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Guatemala and Jennifer Harbury)
    - November 13, 1994 (Box 118)
      (El Sayyid Nosiar's Notebook; American Muslim Community Islamic radicalism)
    - November 27, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Jeanne Moreau)
    - December 18, 1994 (Box 118)
      (Father & Son; William Meyer/Hemlock Society)
    - Reruns and updates, Summer 1995 (Box 119)
  - Season XXVIII, September 1995-April 1996
    - September 17, 1995 (Box 119)
      (Wanted Radovan Karadzic)
    - September 24, 1995 (Box 119)
      (Ben Bradley)
    - October 8, 1995 (Box 119)
      (What about Vince Foster?)
    - October 22, 1995, 2 folders (Box 119)
      (My Fair Lady; Julie Andrews)
    - October 29, 1995 (Box 119)
      (Land mines)
    - November 5, 1995 (Box 119)
      (Yitzhak Rabin)
    - November 26, 1995 (Box 119)
      (Life...by transplant)
    - December 3, 1995 (Box 119)
      (The Last Time We Saw Paris)
    - January 14, 1996 (Box 120)
      (Kidnapped; with Steve Kroft)
    - Starved To Death (Chinese Orphans), January 21, 1996 (Box 120)
    - March 3, 1996/ March 17 (Prison Rape) (Box 120)
    - April 7, 1996 (Box 120)
      (The Mormons)
  - Season XXIX, September 1996-Summer 1997
    - September (?) (Richard Jewell), 1996 (Box 120)
    - September 26 (?) ("Ted's Family" Theodore Kaczynski), 1996 (Box 120)
    - October 10 (?) (Jim Burrows), 1996 (Box 120)
    - October 27, 1996 (Box 120)
      (Columbia HCA Healthcare)
    - November 3, 1996 (Box 121)
      (Nazi Gold)
    - November 10, 1996 (Box 121)
      (Tina Turner)
    - November 17, 1996 (Box 121)
      (Rick Nuccio; State Department envoy to Guatemala who discovered CIA secret regarding killing of Jennifer Harbury's husband, a Guatemalan guerrilla)
    - December 8, 1996 (Box 121)
      ("You Arrogant Journalists"; News Council)
    - December 15, 1996 (Box 121)
      (8 Years and Counting; Libya and Pan Am)
    - December 22, 1996 (Box 121)
      (How Sweet Is It?; Aspartame)
    - January (?) (Mississippi-Trustmark National Bank), 1997 (Box 121)
    - February 2, 1997 (Box 121)
      ("Canada's Dark Secret," Canada as a haven for Nazi war criminals)
    - March 9, 1997 (Box 121)
      ("IPB" Iowa Beef Processors and allegations of dangerous work practices)
    - March 30, 1997 (Box 121)
      (Deadliest Prison; Corcoran)
    - Summer repeats (Box 121)
  - Dead Stories
    - 1981-1984
      - Atlanta (murdered black children and the KKK), 1981 (Box 48)
      - Campaign Money (PACs; Paul Sarbanes versus NCPAC), 1981-1982 (Box 48)
      - Canadian Rescue of Americans (six US diplomats in Iran smuggled out by Canadian Embassy after hostage takeover), 1981 (Box 48)
      - Computerland (William Millard), 1984 (Box 48)
      - Cuba (Institute for Policy Studies' Saul Landau arranging Castro interview), 1982-1983 (Box 48)
      - Futures Scam (commodities futures trading), 1981-1982 (Box 48)
      - Goetz, Bernard, 1984 (Box 48)
      - Holocaust Revisited (revisionism), 1983 (Box 48)
      - Honduras, 1984 (Box 48)
      - Kansas City Mob, undated (Box 48)
      - Land Fraud (worthless US land bought by Europeans), 1983 (Box 48)
      - Lebanon, 1983 (Box 48)
      - Levin, Jeremy (kidnapped CNN bureau chief in Beirut), 1984 (Box 48)
      - Murdoch, Rupert, 1984 (Box 48)
      - NATO, 1982 (Box 48)
      - Nicaragua (CBS Special Reports: Central America), 1982 (Box 48)
      - Nitze, Paul (US Arms Negotiator), 1983 (Box 48)
      - Nuclear Freeze, 1982 (Box 48)
      - Po, 1984 (Box 48)
      - Roche versus Adams (Hoffman/LaRoche Pharmaceuticals versus whistleblower Stanley Adams), 1984 (Box 48)
      - Saudi Arabia, 1983 (Box 48)
      - Savidge, Mark (wrongful murder conviction), 1983 (Box 48)
      - Smalley, Ian (arms merchant), 1982-1983 (Box 48)
      - Soviet Soldiers (in Afghanistan), 1983 (Box 48)
      - Technology Transfer (Soviets buying computer technology), undated (Box 48)
      - Third World Drugging, 1984 (Box 48)
      - von Bulow, Claus, and Allan Dershowitz, 1983 (Box 48)
      - Walker, James Dean, 1984 (Box 48)
      - Wick, Charles, 1984 (Box 48)
      - Wilson, Edwin P. (CIA agent), 1983 (Box 48)
    - 1985-1987
      - Afghanistan, 1987 (Box 48)
      - AIDS, 1987 (Box 48)
      - Aldrich, David (Human Rights in the USSR story idea), 1985 (Box 48)
      - The Ambassador's Wife (US Ambassador to Romania Harry Barnes' wife Elizabeth's affair with Romanian Securitate undercover agent), 1987 (Box 48)
      - Bennett, William J. (US Secretary of Education) background materials; notes, interviews, copy, 1986; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - Bias, Len, 1986 (Box 49)
      - Bio War (biological warfare and the Soviet Union), 1985 (Box 49)
      - Buchanan, Pat, 1985 (Box 49)
      - Capital Punishment, 1985 (Box 49)
      - Cardinal O'Connor, 1987 (Box 49)
      - Center for Defense Information (Star Wars story idea), 1986 (Box 49)
      - Chile, 1986 (Box 49)
      - Claiborne, Judge Harry E. (impeached and convicted federal judge), 1986 (Box 49)
      - Deaver, Mike (lobbying, conflict of interest), 1986 (Box 49)
      - Drug Enforcement Agency and The Mexican Connection (murder of DEA agent Enrique Camarena Salazar; includes newspaper coverage of Wallace preparing story for 60 Minutes), 1986 (Box 49)
      - El Salvador, 1987 (Box 49)
      - Gorbachev, 1986 (Box 49)
      - Hart, Gary, 1987 (Box 49)
      - Hartman, Arthur, US Ambassador to USSR, 1986 (Box 49)
      - High-Tech Baby Boom, 1987 (Box 49)
      - In the Name of Allah (American children abducted by Moslem fathers), 1985 (Box 49)
      - Iran Today, 1985 (Box 49)
      - Iran, 1987 (Box 49)
      - Jinsheng, Wei (Chinese imprisoned dissident), 1986 (Box 49)
      - Korean Olympics, 1987 (Box 49)
      - La Rouche, Lyndon, Jr., 1986 (Box 49)
      - Laxalt, Paul (alleged ties to organized crime), 1984-1986; 2 folders (Box W2)
      - Libya and Qaddafi, 1985 (Box 49)
      - Lucas, Henry Lee, 1985 (Box 49)
      - M-48 Torpedo, 1987 (Box 49)
      - Marcos' Wealth, 1986 (Box 49)
      - Nicaragua, 1985 (Box 49)
      - People versus Sagon Penn (San Diego Police Department and African American man tried for murder), 1987 (Box 49)
      - Philippine Vigilantes, 1987 (Box 49)
      - Pickens, T. Boone, Jr. (Corporate raider), 1985 (Box 49)
      - Posner, Vladimir (Soviet spokesman), 1986 (Box 49)
      - POW/MIAs in Southeast Asia and Bo Gritz, 1986; 2 folders (Box 49)
      - POW/MIAs in Southeast Asia and Bo Gritz, 1986; 1 folder (Box 50)
      - Producer Story Ideas, 1986 (Box 50)
      - Romania, 1987 (Box 50)
      - Savings and Loan Crisis, 1987 (Box 50)
      - Scientific Fraud (Harvard University researchers falsifying data in animal studies funded by NIH grants), 1985 (Box 50)
      - Sharon, Ariel, 1985 (Box 50)
      - Sharansky, Anatoly and Avital (Soviet dissidents), 1986 (Box 50)
      - Singlaub, General Jack (Nicaraguan Contras, World Anti-Communist League; proposed follow-up to 60 Minutes story aired 10/5/86), 1986 (Box 50)
      - South Africa, 1985 (Box 50)
      - Soviet Sports, 1986 (Box 50)
      - Spain, Johnny (San Quentin), 1986 (Box 50)
      - A Town Gone Bad (Everglades City, Florida, and drug smuggling), 1985 (Box 50)
      - Turks and Caicos Islands, 1985 (Box 50)
      - UNESCO, 1985-1986 (Box 50)
      - Union Carbide, 1986 (Box 50)
      - Vivas, Felix (correspondence received), 1985-1986 (Box 50)
      - Wal-Mart, 1985 (Box 50)
      - Ward, Michael (producer; various story ideas), 1986 (Box 50)
      - Wilson, Edwin P. (CIA agent in prison), 1986 (Box 50)
      - Worthy, William (story ideas), 1986 (Box 50)
      - Zion's Troubled Children ("Israel's new generation of racists"), 1986 (Box 50)
    - 1988-1991
      - Agnelli, Giovanni (Fiat), 1988 (Box 50)
      - Akhromeyev, Sergei, Marshall, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Baxter Boycott (Pharmaceutical supply company and bribes to trade with Arab countries), 1991 (Box 50)
      - Beirut, 1990 (Box 50)
      - The Black Budget (Pentagon's secret treasury), 1990 (Box 50)
      - Blacks in the Military, 1991 (Box 50)
      - Black Studies, 1990 (Box 50)
      - Bluesheets (miscellaneous), 1990 (Box 50)
      - Bombay, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Brawley, Tawana, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Brunei-Crisis in Paradus, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Bush, Barbara, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Chapman, Tracy, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Children of the Intifada, 1989 (Box 50)
      - China with Nixon (proposed accompanying Nixon on trip to China), 1989 (Box 50)
      - Cocaine chemistry, 1989 (Box 50)
      - The Collaborators (Palestinian collaboration with Israelis), 1989 (Box 50)
      - Combat Stress, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Faked Footage (Afghanistan), 1989 (Box 50)
      - Germany Reunified?, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Hong Kong Boat People, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Horne, Marilyn, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Howard, Dan, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Hussein, Saddam, 1991 (Box 50)
      - Iran-President Hojatolislam Hashemi Rafsanjani, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Ishihara, Shintaro (Japanese politician), 1989 (Box 50)
      - The Ivory Slaughter (African elephants), 1989 (Box 50)
      - The Joint Commission on Accreditation of Healthcare Organizations (Hospital accreditation and negligence in Texas; Suzanne St. Pierre produced extensive background materials for this story), 1989 (Box 50)
      - Jordan-Yossi Melman, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Lehder, Carlos (imprisoned Latin American--Colombian?; several exchanges of correspondence trying to get an interview with him), 1989-1990 (Box 50)
      - Lithuania (Eastern Bloc Nationalism), 1988 (Box 50)
      - Madonna, 1991 (Box 50)
      - Maritime Crime (late, undated; 1988 (Box 50)
      - McFerrin, Bobby, 1989 (Box 50)
      - Memphis Cops, 1989; 2 folders (Box 50)
      - Menuhin, Yehudi, 1991 (Box 50)
      - Missile Smuggling, 1988 (Box 50)
      - Morales, Santiago, 1989 (Box 50)
      - My Lai, 1988 (Box 50)
      - The Networks (underground anti-Communist organizations), 1990 (Box 50)
      - Oakland Housing Authority security force, 1990 (Box 50)
      - Obeid, Sheik Abdul, 1989 (Box 50)